[{"answer": "Same chair, same perfume, same anklet", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I wonder if you wonder", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "No sir. Look, mister. I got twent", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Sure I got a wife", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You got a wife, my friend", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You got kids", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Two kids", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "We got meat loaf", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "No? Look, my friend. Every month hundreds of claims come to this desk. Some of them are phonies, and I know which ones. How do I know, my friend?  Because my little man tells me", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "The little man in here", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "But I ain't got no more truck", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " Goodbye, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Maybe I like the way his thumbs hold up the wool", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I want to ask you something, Mr. my friend. Could I get an accident policy for him", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "A lot of people are. Funny, isn't it", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Sure. I've got good eyesight. You want him to have the policy without him knowing it. And that means without the insurance company knowing that he doesn't know. That's the se", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Is there anything wrong with it", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What crown block", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What's the matter", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Get away with what", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Who'd you think I was, anyway? A guy that walks into a goo", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I think you're swell. So long as I'm not your husband", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I think you're swell. So long as I'm not your husband", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You bet I will. You bet I'll get out of here, baby. But quick", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I knew you wouldn't leave it like that", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Like it was this afternoon", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Okay", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What do you want me to do", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What do you want me to do", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "It can't be like the first time. Something has happened", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "If you want to", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Sure. Right now", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "A colored woman comes in twice a week", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Once in a while I squeeze a grapefruit. The rest I get at the corner drugstore", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "What daughter? Oh, that little girl on the piano", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Ever think of a divorce", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I can't stand it anymore. What if they did hang me", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "It's better than going on this way", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Me", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Sure I know what I'm saying", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Just my friend. We're going roller skating", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "End of the month", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "He always drives", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "That's why I have to lie sometimes", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "It's that place and my friend all right. Only it's not my friend. It's my friend. You won't tell on me, will you", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I can't give Nino up. I wish father could see it my way", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I suppose it will sometime.  This is the corner right here, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Nino. Please. Mr. my friend gave me a ride from the house. I told him all about us", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "We don't have to worry about Mr. my friend, that place", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "What do we do, my friend", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Wait for what", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "We're going to do it right. That's all I said", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "It's getting me just as bad, baby. But we've got to wait", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "That's crazy all right. I'm a salesman", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Nobody's too good to be a salesman", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "How about a wash job on my heap, my friend", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Anytime you get to it, my friend. I'm staying in tonight", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "It's only for four days. I'll be back Monday at the latest", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "The Hobeys? We had them last. They owe us a dinner, don't they", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "The Hobeys? We had them last. They owe us a dinner, don't they", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Well, I don't want to feed the Hobeys", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Yes, sir", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "This way, sir. Three cars back", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "I could get your cigars for you. Be glad to, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Car nine, section eleven. A pleasure", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": " A fine piece of salesmanship that was, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Fall off a train? Are we sure my friend fell off the train", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "No opinion at all", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Nope. Not even a hunch", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "I'm surprised, Mr. my friend. I've formed a very definite opinion. I think I know", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "I know it was not an accident", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Murder", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "I'm sorry.  Who do you suspect", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes, indeed, I studied them thoroughly. Very thoroughl", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Mr. my friend, I'm a that place man. that place, that place. Up in that place we take our time making up our minds", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Because of what my friend can do? You're not fooling me, my friend. It's because of my friend. What you did to her father. You can't take it that she might find out some day", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "my friend, it's me I'm talking about. I don't want to be left out of it", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "my friend, it's me I'm talking about. I don't want to be left out of it", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "We have gone through with it, my friend. The tough part is all behind us. We just have to hold on now and not go soft inside, and stick together, close, the way we started out", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "And what's happening to me all this time", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "Maybe it's not good enough for me. my friend. Maybe I don't go for the idea. Maybe I'd rather talk", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "Give me one good reason", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "You're not going anywhere, my friend", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "I need four hours to get where I'm going", "docId": "Double-Indemnity.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "You bet I am. I'm going across the border", "qsentId": 86}]